busycreatingmemories.com 2017-01-19

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy

 **Busy Creating Memories  respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Busy Creating Memories.

Any information gathered for Giveaways is used solely for the purpose of contacting the winner to claim their prize and to allow the sponsor to award the prize to the winner. No other purpose for your information will be used.

 **Credit card details**

Busy Creating Memories will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Busy Creating Memories.

 **External Sites.**

Busy Creating Memories is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party webeacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

 **Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Busy Creating Memories to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Busy Creating Memories does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

 **Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Busy Creating Memories and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Busy Creating Memories have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:amber@busycreatingmemories.com) 

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.
